Heywood Greater Manchester - UK +4407514770836 yve.jessica@gmail.com github.com/jessicayve

#### SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS
- Javascript
- React.JS
- Styled-Components
- React Hooks
- REST
- Restful
- HTTP
- Jest
- Node.JS
- Knex
- Typescript
- MySQL
- AWS
- SQL
- Github
- Firebase
- Unit testing

# JESSICA YVE

## FULL STACK DEVELOPER ABOUT ME

After working as an administrative assistant for several years, I realized that my true passion lay in web development. I began teaching myself coding in my free time and eventually I enrolled in a coding bootcamp and quickly proved to be a skilled and dedicated learner. I became proficient in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and several programming languages, and honed mine skills in responsive web design, database management, and server-side programming. I credit my background in administration for giving me strong organizational skills and attention to detail, which I apply to my work as a developer.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### Labenu

FULL-STACK WEB DEVELOPMENT BOOTCAMP, AUGUST/2022 - FEBRUARY/2023

Program with over 1000 hours of hands-on experience in Full-stack development, guided by agile methodologies (Kanban/Scrum).

Among the skills learned during the course are HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Styled-Components, React Hooks, REST, Api Restful, HTTP

Jest, Node.JS, Knex, TypeScript, MySQL, AWS, SQL, Git, Github, Firebase,

Unit Testing and UI Design.

#### Catholic University of Brasília

BUSINESS SCHOOL 02/2009 - 06/2012

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### CNI - National Confederation of Industry (Brazil)

ADMINISTRATIVE ASSISTANT - 04/2012 - 06/2013

Support for administrative management.

### SESI - INDUSTRY SOCIAL SERVICE/ NATIONAL DEPARTMENT

INTERNSHIP 05/2010 - 06/2011

Support for SESI's national sports manager.